<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TravelgateX Documentation – Web travelgatex.com changelog</title>
    <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/</link>
    <description>Recent changes in Web travelgatex.com changelog on TravelgateX Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://docs.travelgatex.com/img/hugo.png</url>
      <title>GoHugo.io</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/</link>
    </image>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: 2019-10-15</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-10-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-10-15/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
         2019-10-15  ACCESES: Added shared field and allowed url edition in acceses. MENU: new horizontal menu.    CONNECT: Modified to choose client before hotelx. PUBLIC WEB: changed info searches/day in home.    PROFILES: tag error on removing category fixed. PRESS: Fixed media processing.   
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: 2019-10-09</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-10-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-10-09/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
         2019-10-09  ALERTS: Added new filters and group by ALERTS: Add API and timesToRecovery    ALERTS: Added new responsive styles    ALERTS: fix on Status ALERTS: fix on Update Price   
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: 2019-09-16</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-09-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-09-16/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
         2019-09-16  Connect: Added VCC to legacy Profiles: Enabled entity asignment to profiles IAM: Added pagination and info to orgs, and profiles page completed    Added gzip compression to calls to the gateway    Alerts: Fixed issue on create new alert Connect: Fixed dates activations   
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: 2019-09-30</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-09-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-09-30/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
         2019-09-30  ENTITIES: Modified access form to custom require runtime configuration    IAM: Changes on new macro roles ORGANIZATIONS: Changed filters to not appear on the request on missing    MEMBERS: Solved an error realated on updating api-keys after a new creation   
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: 2019-08-30</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-08-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-08-30/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
         2019-08-30  IAM: Added owner filter to entities/admin-entities. added new tab for&amp;hellip; Logging: Added hotel reference Members: IAM-macro-roles, added tabs for simple and advanced Alerts: entities by buyer or seller    Logging: References now allows more than one option    Logging: Fixed logging with filter if your not logged on the page   
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: 2019-08-16</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-08-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-08-16/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
         2019-08-16  Logging: Added new feature to set filters via url Alerts: added logic time alerts Connect: modified profile cals and addded premium partner option to connect    Accesses: improved refresh logic when updating accesses IAM Entities: Improved sorting in entities    B2B: Fixed required typename on apis   
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: 2019-07-31</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-07-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-07-31/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
         2019-07-31  Alerts: Added sort to table Stats: traffic type selector Logging: Added column machine to results Logging: Selector items per page Error Messages: added hint description to error code table    Changed format of api-errors    Logging: Fixed error descriptions Profiles: fixed bug that prevented refresh on edit Logging: Added label when reference filters are disabled   
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: 2019-07-15</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-07-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-07-15/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
         2019-07-15  Alerts: added configuration multiselectors Profiles: Fully enabled filter profiles Logging: Added new filter number of results Entities: Added sorting method Profiles: Updated query to look for stats and formated text in profiles    Logging: Filter errors refactored Logging: Added red control to non filled required filters Logging: Changed time to 24h mode, without am/pm    Logging: Logging table wasn&amp;rsquo;t showing the timestamps on firefox, now is fixed Logging: Enable showing organisation suppliers on SELLER mode Logging: Hide the table on no results   
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: 2019-06-28</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-06-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/2019-06-28/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
         2019-06-28  Logging-filter: Implemented ShowOnlyActives filter, added pagination to the results table Added Star-rating component at pages and changed text in people Created internal status page Alerts released on web    Logging-filter: Reorder filter columns, reorder table columns Changed the global header, alerts and organization selector.    Fix on Stats Calendar   
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: travelgatex.com</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/legacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/release-notes/products-changelogs/changelog-web/log/legacy/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        To make it easier for users and contributors to see precisely what notable changes have been made on the web.
Web site Link
All notable changes to this product will be documented in this page.2019-06-20  TEAMs: Improved TEAMs page to allow see teams to all TGX operators Stats: Now shows totals and percentatge on all headers IAM Members: Added icon type members to be more clean IAM Members: Improvement to keep groups open at IAM page    Profiles: Revised redirections to all profile pages IAM Members: fixed creation of new members solving issue on granting permissions IAM create organization: New organizations, pattern code has been changed to allow numbers on organization code Stats: stats view all adviseMessages and only reject if error   2019-06-06  IAM admin entities: UX improve, now expanded by default    IAM admin entities: The accesses list weren&amp;rsquo;t showing the supplier data asociated Stats: stats view all adviseMessages and only reject if error   2019-05-29  IAM members: added macro-roles for distribution IAM members: added macro-roles for alerts and agrupations IAM: added &amp;ldquo;suit organization&amp;rdquo; option to adapt organizations to IAM tree structure.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>