<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TravelgateX Documentation – Insights-X</title>
    <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/insights-x/</link>
    <description>Recent changes in Insights-X on TravelgateX Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://docs.travelgatex.com/img/hugo.png</url>
      <title>GoHugo.io</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/insights-x/</link>
    </image>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://docs.travelgatex.com/insights-x/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights-X: Overview</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/insights-x/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/insights-x/overview/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        In order to analyze and produce useful insights, Insights-X extracts, loads and consolidates data from products like Hotel-X.
Once the data is consolidated in our Data warehouse, we can share data depending on each partner&amp;rsquo;s relationship with TravelgateX:
 Partners: e.g. OTAs and Wholesalers already connected to our platform, they will have access to accurate data regarding their performance, ratios, prices, product usage&amp;hellip; With these insights an accurate benchmarking against competitors is provided so that our partners can gain a competitive advantage.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights-X: Contents</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/insights-x/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/insights-x/content/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        What is the performance of your infrastructure? What hotelier product is being requested and booking around the world? How are you doing with respect to your competitors?
Knowledge is power and that&amp;rsquo;s what the product Insights-X offers, based on more than 2 billion search requests and more than 20,000 bookings per day.
In order to answer the three previous questions, the product has been designed in three parts, which we explain below:
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights-X: FAQs</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/insights-x/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/insights-x/faqs/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        In order to analyze and access useful insights, we recommend you to read Insights-X FAQs.
* Data sets and Reporting:  How do I get access to my data sets?  Insights-X data sets are stored in BigQuery. Once Insights-X is acquired, we will provide you with the credentials to access and connect to the database with your data sets.
 How often are the data sets updated?  Insights-X stores data from all transactions passing through TravelgateX.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>