<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TravelgateX Documentation – Tutorials</title>
    <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent changes in Tutorials on TravelgateX Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://docs.travelgatex.com/img/hugo.png</url>
      <title>GoHugo.io</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/tutorials/</link>
    </image>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: Build An OTA</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/tutorials/ota-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/tutorials/ota-site/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Creating your full OTA This topic describes how to build your own OTA using HotelX.
Before you begin  Basic knowledge of Angular Read HotelX, which contains information about the HotelX API  Scenario: Create an Online Travel Agency written in Angular For this quickstart tutorial, we have prepared a repository that contains the full Angular code for the OTA clone. All you need to do is to get TravelgateX credentials and connect it with the Angular application.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: Configure HotelX Security</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/tutorials/howto-configure-permissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/tutorials/howto-configure-permissions/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Granting Permissions This topic describes how to configure permissions for a organization using HotelX and Stats.
Before you begin  Read IAM, which contains information about how TravelgateX manages security Read HotelX, which contains information about the HotelX API  Scenario: Organization buying suppliers through HotelX In this scenario, organanization org_test logs on to TravelgateX in order to use HotelX to buy product from suppliers.
Distribution will be made through 2 different channels, end users will use org_test_B2C_site whereas that org_test_B2B_site will be used for business users.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>