<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TravelgateX Documentation – Security</title>
    <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/security/</link>
    <description>Recent changes in Security on TravelgateX Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://docs.travelgatex.com/img/hugo.png</url>
      <title>GoHugo.io</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/security/</link>
    </image>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: Overview</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/security/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/security/overview/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        This page describes the how security is implemented in TravelgateX platform.
Introduction TravelgateX offers a fine-grained access control and visibility for centrally managing Resources, which are granted to Partners belonging to Organizations.
Authentication Authentication is the process of authorizing or making sure that the Partner is the correct one. Every request to TravelgateX GraphQL API must carry an Access Token whether it&amp;rsquo;s an API Key or a JSON Web Token (JWT).
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelgatex: Identity and access management</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/security/identity-access-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/travelgatex/security/identity-access-management/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        This section provides an overview of Identity and access management.
TravelgateX identity and acccess management lets administrators authorize who can take action on specific resources, giving you full control and internal visibility to manage resources centrally.
Identity and access management provides an unified view of your security policy across your entire organization, with built-in auditing to ease compliance processes.
As an administrator, when you register with us, we provide you with login details to access your TravelgateX account, including a username and password.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>