<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TravelgateX Documentation – Booking Flow Methods</title>
    <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/</link>
    <description>Recent changes in Booking Flow Methods on TravelgateX Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://docs.travelgatex.com/img/hugo.png</url>
      <title>GoHugo.io</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/</link>
    </image>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Avail</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/avail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/avail/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to return all the available options for a given date and itinerary. It does not filter different classes, times or fares. It will always retrieve all results returned by the supplier.
Request Format The availability request is very straight forward. It only requires destination, travel dates and the number of pax in each room.
Response Format Results are organized in this hierarchy=
 Hotel :  A list with all the hotels, including hotel name and code, mealplans list, etc.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Valuation</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/valuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/valuation/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to return the total price and cancellation policies of the Option selected in the previous step (Avail).
Request Format The Valuation request format is similar to that of availabilityRQ. It&amp;rsquo;s here you will add data to the option selected.
Response Format The returned XML contains the total price and list of cancellation policies.
Remarks Our system allows for a maximum of 180000 milliseconds before the connection is closed.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Reservation</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/reservation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/reservation/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to book an option.
Request Format The request format works the same way as Valuation but with the list of passengers.
Response Format The result returns the booking locator (booking code), which could be the supplier&amp;rsquo;s own code or the one sent in request.
It also returns all the charges associated with the booking as well as its status.
Remarks 180000 milliseconds is the maximum amount of time permitted in our system before the connection is closed.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Cancel</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/cancel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/cancel/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to cancel a booking
Request Format The request requires one or more of the following data, depending on the supplier:
 Locators: booking codes - this element contains two elements, Client (client&amp;rsquo;s booking code) and Provider (supplier&amp;rsquo;s booking code). One or both will be required depending on the supplier hotelCode: the hotel code StartDate: the check-in date EndDate: the check-out date  Response Format The result returns a response with the booking status, the cancellation&amp;rsquo;s ID and the fee for that cancellation.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: ReservationRead</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/reservationread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/reservationread/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to retrieve detailed information about a specific Reservation
Request Format The request requires one of the following data depending on supplier:
 Locators: booking codes (this element contains two elements Client (client&amp;rsquo;s booking code) and Provider (supplier&amp;rsquo;s booking code), one or both will be required depending on the supplier) Currency: the currency code CreationDate: the booking date StardDate: the check-in date EndDate: the check-out date HotelCode: Hotel code  Response Format The result returns the full details of a booking.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: ReservationList</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/reservationlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/hotel-suppliers/methods/messages/booking-flow-methods/reservationlist/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to return a list of bookings for a given time period being that either booking date or the travelling date.
Request Format The request requires one of the following data depending on provider:
 DateType: indicates the date type: either booking creation date or booking start date Start: the date from End: the date to  Response Format The result returns a list of bookings details, with the same format as ReservationReadRS.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>