<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TravelgateX Documentation – Ferries API</title>
    <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/</link>
    <description>Recent changes in Ferries API on TravelgateX Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://docs.travelgatex.com/img/hugo.png</url>
      <title>GoHugo.io</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/</link>
    </image>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Availability</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/avail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/avail/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to complete the common side of the petition with the ferries specifications, if any, and therefore have the complete petition for ferries.
Request Format The request needs a list of journeys (each one with the desired dates and ports), a list of the passengers and an optional vehicle list.
Response Format The response contains a list of fares with the available options.
AvailabilityRQ &amp;lt;AvailabilityRQ xmlns:xsd = &amp;quot;http://www.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Cancellation</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/cancel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/cancel/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to cancel a booking.
Request Format The request requires the booking code or locator.
Response Format If the provider returns a Breakdown, this will be informed in CancellarionRS.
CancellationRQ Example &amp;lt;CancellationRQ&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Locator&amp;gt;XXX&amp;lt;/Locator&amp;gt; &amp;lt;CancellationCosts&amp;gt;0&amp;lt;/CancellationCosts&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/CancellationRQ&amp;gt;  CancellationRQ Description    Element Number Type Description     CancellationRQ 1  Root node.   Locator 1  Contains a list of Tickets.   CancellationCosts 1  Contains details of the Ticket.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Common Elements</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/common-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/common-elements/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Introduction In every petition there some nodes which will always appear, there for this chapter is dedicated for said nodes.
Request Format The common elements in all of the petitions are: source of the petition, Timeout, the indication if you wish to register the transactions and the provider configuration.
Response Format The response will contain the indication if the function is implemented or not, application errors, if any, the providers traces if requested and the response status.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Errors</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/error/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/error/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Error description    Possible Values Description     102 Supplier Error.   103 Duplicate Booking.   104 Supplier connection error.   105 Generic communication error.   188 Availability product not found.   191 Unknown error or Integration/Application error.   210 Payment card error.   211 Passenger error.   212 Delta price error.   345 Connection timeout.   346 Operation not implemented.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Ferries Data Structure</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/ferriesdatastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/ferriesdatastructure/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        The structure of the API specification follows a standard. This document intends to explain every aspect of this structure and their fields.
The integration will have the following methods:
   Method Input Output Required Description     Avail AvailabilityRQ AvailabilityRS Yes Makes a availability call   Valuation ValuationRQ ValuationRS Yes Makes a pre-booking   Reservation ReservationRQ ReservationRS Yes Makes a booking   Routes RoutesRQ RoutesRS Yes Gets a static routes list   RetrieveReservation RetrieveReservation RQ RetrieveReservation RS No Gets the details of a single booking   RetrieveReservation List RetrieveReservation ListRQ RetrieveReservation ListRS No Gets a list of bookings   Cancelation CancellationRQ CancellationRS No Cancels a booking    Each request sent to the service url requires a node called rqXML .
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Reservation</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/reservation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/reservation/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to book one or more itineraries.
Request Format The request format works the same way as the Valuation request. It can work with one Itinerary or with two.
This request also holds the passengers and payment data.
Response Format The result returns a list of Locator (booking codes). It can be the supplier&amp;rsquo;s or the one sent in the request. It also returns all the charges associated to the booking.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: RetrieveReservation</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/retrievereservation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/retrievereservation/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to retrieve a booking with its full details.
Request Format The request requires the booking code or locator.
Response Format The response contains the details of a booking.
RetrieveReservationRQ Example &amp;lt;RetrieveReservationRQ xmlns:xsd = &amp;quot;http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema&amp;quot; xmlns:xsi = &amp;quot;http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Configuration/&amp;gt; &amp;lt;ClientConfiguration/&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Locator&amp;gt;BFRFKVM&amp;lt;/Locator&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/RetrieveReservationRQ&amp;gt;  RetrieveReservationRQ Description    Element Number Type Description     RetrieveReservationRQ 1  Root node.   Locator 1 String Locator.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: RetrieveReservationList</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/retrievereservationlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/retrievereservationlist/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to return a list of bookings for a given time period being that either booking date or the travelling date.
Request Format The request requires a date (of reservation or departure) and all the bookings that match this date will be returned.
Response Format The response contains a list of bookings that match the requested date.
RetrieveReservationListRQ Example &amp;lt;RetrieveReservationListRQ&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Configuration/&amp;gt; &amp;lt;ClientConfiguration currencyCode = &amp;quot;EUR&amp;quot;/&amp;gt; &amp;lt;ReservationDate&amp;gt;2014-03-04T00:00:00&amp;lt;/ReservationDate&amp;gt; &amp;lt;DepartureDate&amp;gt;2010-09-09T00:00:00&amp;lt;/DepartureDate&amp;gt; &amp;lt;ClientEmail&amp;gt;client@clientmail.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Routes</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/routes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/routes/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to return all the available routes for the selected carrier.
Request Format This request does not require any parameters.
Response Format The result returns a list of Route with the corresponding time frame in which this route is valid.
Remarks This method should be cached internally and only called once a week and in most cases once a month.
RoutesRQ Example &amp;lt;RoutesRQ&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/RoutesRQ&amp;gt;  RoutesRQ Description    Element Number Type Description     RoutesRQ 1  Root node.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy: Valuation</title>
      <link>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/valuation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.travelgatex.com/legacy/transportation/ferries/valuation/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        Method Goals This method aims to do a prebook of the selected Option. This Option must be selected in the previous step ( Availability ).
The Valuation request must be built from results of a single Availability. Mixing OneWay options from different Availability calls do not grant the correct functionability of the Valuation.
Request Format The Valuation request can be done by two different ways: with a single Itinerary or multiple Itineraries.
        
          [...]
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>